When I was a child,
the world looked like a much simpler place.
There were no unbeatable challenges
and a hard work is something
that will always be rewarded.
The world is simple and clear:
you win, you lose, or it ends in a draw.
I need more precise moves.
I need more efficient tactics.
I need a superior strategy!
Even when you're up against the best,
just continue experimenting
until you can win the next time.
Such foolish, ignorant youth.
That's what I thought.
That view was nothing but an illusion,
a child's worthless fantasy world.
The truth is,
this world,
beside being chaotic with its events,
is also filled with coincidences,
unreasonable,
absurd,
and didn't even have a meaning.
That's why...
the next time,
next time for sure—
Elkia
Why?
Why can't I win?!
Not to brag or anything,
but I've been only defeated once in my entire life.
The sixth of the ten pledges:
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
"Any bets made in accordance
with the pledges must be upheld."
This law is absolute, per the One True God who rules our world.
I'll crush you...
Next time for sure, I'll definitely crush you!
"Next time for sure", huh?
If you couldn't beat these two, you don't stand a chance with me.
Sora and Shiro, do you know them?
All right, during the next game,
I will tell you an interesting story while we play.
As a thanks for your snack just now.
You're just trying to distract me, please.
If you want to talk, then just talk, please.
Great, then I will!
Since it's an ancient myth that
has never been told by anyone.
I'm not listening, please.
So...
this story happened over six thousand years ago.
A bitter war raged,
ravaging the Earth and extinguishing the planets.
As time passed, no one remembers it anymore.
And yet,
it's a one tale that I will never forget.
It's a big one.
The black ash is falling, hurry up.
Ivan?
I'm okay.
What about the spirit compas?
It's like this, due to the black ash.
We need to rely on our senses for this one.
Don't let your guard down.
Riku!
Come here quick! There's a—
This is—
This is a dwarven world map and it looks like it's the latest version!
That's not all.
It shows the balance of power between
the races and even the Dwarves' strategy.
Ivan, Aley,
compare this to what we've
got and make corrections.
I'll try to make sense of this.
Aschieto!
A message... from the Dwarves?
Fusion...
detonation?
How much of this world do they
plan to destroy?!
Let's get out of here!
Aley, don't take anything that uses spiritual energy.
But!
You wanna die, just say so.
Fuck!
Ivan,
this is an order.
Die here.
Aschieto.
Ivan!
Take care of my kid.
Sorry, Riku—
The bait is here! Come and get me Demonia!
They say there used to be something called "the sun".
Its' white flames lit the Heavens,
turning the skies into the most
brilliant blue you've ever seen.
An uplifting story...
like something out of a fairytale.
Gods and their creations waged eternal war.
The Earth burned, choking the heavens with soot
and raining down the ashes of the dead spirits.
Riku!
These ashes...
it's the least we can do to honor them,
I guess—
No-n-na!
Here.
Oh wow! That's my name! Does this read "Nonna"?
Hey! I wanna see my name too!
I was first, Couronne.
Sure,
one at a time.
Couronne! They're back!
Riku!
Riku, thank goodness.
Couronne.
Come on, you're way too late! Were you
trying to give me a heart attack?
And seriously, how many times I have to tell you to call me big sis?
We came back as fast as we could.
About Ivan—
Riku!
Daddy!
Nonna!
Riku, Aley, welcome back! Where is daddy?
I want to show him the letter I wrote myself! Where is Daddy?
Nonna—
Listen to me, Nonna.
Riku...
Nonna.
Your dad...
won't be coming home.
W-why?
Because he's dead.
You're lying!
It's not a lie.
You're lying! Daddy promised me he will come back home!
He said that in the end the humans will win!
We will win.
That's why your dad fought with all he could.
So the rest of us could win.
That's not winning!
It should have been you—
You're the one who should have died!
Nonna!
Why don't you two go take a bath?
I'll dust myself off.
No, take a bath.
You guys stink.
So we could—
So we could win?
I'm a god damn hypocrite!
Ivan threw his life away!
I told him to die!
Say it out loud
"I killed him, just so I could live
a little longer!"
If we keep on these rules...
where does it lead?
How long will this continue?
Do we kill 999 people for the sake of saving 1001?
Or we kill until there is only one left?
When will this ever end?
How long will I have to...
keep lying myself like this?
No one born into this world,
could die without a reason.
It's more than simply having a reason to live.
The mind will not accept death,
if it has no meaning.
I won't let Ivan's death be in vain.
Reliable information from
the ruins of the elvish city,
things that most people never get a chance to see.
When one keeps seeking for a purpose in a world like this.
Is it even possible to still call that a sanity?
The Dwarves?
No.
The scale of this destruction...
must have been the Flügel.
Look at the size of this thing...
My... imagination?
Ex-machina?!
Investigating.
Adjusting to the circumstances.
Stay calm.
This thing always operates as a part of a collective.
It shares consciousness with a cluster,
which means others must be nearby.
That means—
Conclusion.
If I make any hostile moves,
all the Ex-machinas will see me as a threat.
I must not resist.
Onii-chan, I cannot resist you.
Make a woman out of me.
Huh?
Error:
Cannot
comprehend.
I am the one that cannot fucking comprehend here!
Conjecture: Is this scenario not sufficient
to bring you gratification?
Unfortunately...
I'm not a weirdo that gets excited
by being observed by you guys.
Query:
Who are "you guys"?
Oh don't play dumb with me.
I know all of this gets sent to that cluster thing of yours.
Negative.
This unit has been disengaged
from the cluster collective.
Disengaged you say?
So that means you're alone?
Affirmative.
So then...
What does some stray Ex-machina
want with someone like me?
Do you mind if I even ask?
Response:
To analyze the unique language
humans use among themselves.
The language referred to as "the heart".
The heart?
Reasoning:
This unit's investigation of the heart generated multiple
logic errors, causing this unit to be disassociated.
Therefore further observation
has been conducted independently.
Observation?
So, you're planning to study the heart on your own
and get the cluster to take you back, right?
Demand:
It is postulated that dermo-contact, flesh upon flesh,
results in a unique exchange of emotions.
I request you procreate with this unit.
I refuse.
Alternative:
You may take advantage of
this unit in any manner you wish.
Though it possesses no orifice.
I already said—
Wait, no orifice?
Lösen.
Recreation.
Earth.
Chess.
A challenge.
I request participation in the game.
Conditions:
If this unit wins, it shall be taken home
with you and procreation will occur.
Of all things, you chose chess?
You guys are basically walking calculators.
There is no way I can win.
But—
What if I—
do manage to win?
Answer:
You shall take this unit home and then
permission for procreation shall be granted.
There's no difference!
Well whatever, I guess there's no
other way out of this, is there?
Fine, I'll play along.
Conclusion:
A game in accordance to the aforementioned terms.
Sure, I'll play with you one time.
Except I'll be making a slight change
to these little win conditions of yours.
We have arrived.
So, when it comes to mobility you
really don't use any spiritual energy?
Correct.
Utilizing spiritual energy would
have saved 55.782 seconds.
Addendum:
This unit is a Prüfer, a model primarily used for analysis.
It's capabilities are less than other Ex-machinas'.
Having an absurd race like this waging a war?
No wonder the world has gone to hell.
What should I call you?
Meaning unknown.
Your name. Do you have one?
Understood.
Designation number:
ÜC207PR4F57T9.
Are you kidding?
Forget that, you're gonna need to go
with something easier.
Reminder:
This unit won, so it will stay with Riku until it
is able to fully comprehend the human heart.
Should this unit conceal it is a machine?
The heart is like an unspoken feeling.
It is formed through mutual understanding.
And if you're gonna be with me,
you need to dress like a human.
Query: Is self-naming allowed?
Sure, whatever.
Response:
I shall be called Schwarzer.
No way! Hard to say and sounds weird.
Let's just go with Schwi.
Inconsistency:
Adjustment was made for my composed name.
Before we enter...
can we do something with your talking?
Laden: Adopting personality 1610.
Hehe. Onii-chan, is this better?
No way!
Retort: It was the most logical choice available.
And what logical bullcrap did you use
to position yourself as my younger sister?
Answer: I merely presented the most optimal option.
It will be a big problem if people start asking about our past.
Just act shy and don't say more than you have to.
And quit starting every sentence
sounding like a robot. Understood?
Understood.
Is this fine?
Are you... acting?
Acting?
I'm not.
I have chosen a personality
matching the given parameters
Trace emulation.
It'll do.
I want you to stay where I can
see you and keep those clothes on.
Is there something you can do
about that tail looking thing you got there?
Negative.
It is Schwi's power source.
A quasi-nerve crossed with spiritual circuitry.
Fine, I guess.
We'll just say it's a fashion choice.
But I'm gonna say this one more time:
You can't show that robot body of yours to anyone else.
Ok.
Can only show it to you.
She's so cute!
Who is this girl?
I found her on the way back
in a colony that got wiped out, she was in a—
So she is...
your wife?
Wife?
Listen—
Oh come on! Don't be shy!
In this age your first priority should be kids,
second is food, three, four, five is more kids!
Could you stop that?
That goes for you too!
What does she mean?
She doesn't mean anything.
What's your name?
I'm Schwi.
That's a lovely name.
So how did you meet Riku?
We kissed... and then... a demand for the procretion was made.
No, that's not—
Riku.
Couldn't you wait...
at least until you go back?!
You could have worded that in a better way you know?
"Better way"?
Never mind.
Look, could you at least try to look a bit more mature?
You've already made me look bad over here.
Isn't it the form that you prefer?
Nah, I don't have that kind of taste.
Then, what form do you like?
Now, you listen here.
Do you even know what "like"
means when you ask that question?
I'm wanting to know what you "like".
That's not something I can really tell you with words.
Do you remember how I explained the human heart?
Then,
let's play a game.
I refuse.
That time I didn't have much of a choice.
But I find games pointless and
I don't have time to waste on them.
What if it won't be pointless?
What if you win
and the prize will be all the information you desire.
For example,
the reason why the Great War began
and what it will take to end it.
Give me a break.
As a mere human,
I have no interest nor is it necessary to know that.
There is only one thing I need to know:
How to make it through the day alive.
And that's it.
That's the whole reason I brought you along.
The knowledge, the maths,
the engineering tech you ex-machina contain—
If I would beat you then that's what I want.
Understood.
Currently...
the state of our world...
the fact that humans still exist is...
an anomaly.
Even we, Ex-machina...
cannot calculate a reason for this.
As life forms you are weak.
Your civilization is primitive.
You cannot utilize spiritual power, and yet...
You have subsisted.
There must be a reason,
a key...
to your survival.
And my theory is that...
it resides...
in the human heart.
Schwi wish to discover—
Stop.
Don't mock me.
Riku?
You wage war whenever you want.
You rob us of everything we have.
And what you have to say is:
"Hey humans, why do you guys still exist?"
"Let me see what's in your heart."
Yeah?!
You wanna know?!
What comes from my heart...
since the very day I was born?!
Rot in hell! Every fucking one of you!
Do you know how many people
have died because of you?
You probably know exaclty how many, don't you?
And how many will die because of my rules?
Riku.
You cry.
Therefore...
I assume...
I have said something terrible.
Something... to hurt you.
Riku's heart
wish to kill Schwi.
Understood.
If you just
stab me here,
Schwi
will die.
Die?
Since I am not a living being,
a permament cessation,
impossible to repair.
Termination.
Schwi wish to know Riku's heart.
That's why...
If this is truly what your heart desires. I want to know...
Will you...
kill Schwi?
Chad
Anton
Elmer
Cory
Dale
Siris
Ed
Darrell
Dave
Laks
Vin
Eric
Charlie
Riku?
Thomson
Shinta
Yann
Zaza
Zargo
Clay
Goro
Peter
Arthur
Morg
Kimmy
Datt
Ceril
Vigi
Volly
Ken
Savage
Leroy
Popo
Couthon
Lut
Shigure
Shao
Ulf
Balto
Asso
Kenwood
Peyl
Ahad
Hound
Balrof
Masashi
Memegan
Karim!
Ivan!
Forty-eight people.
It's forty-eight people that I ordered to die.
Many people have
died because of your Great War.
Removed, like dust being swept away!
But...
the one who convinced them
that they need to die—
Riku?
You awake?
Sorry, I know you're tired, but if you don't mind—
Oh! Sorry!
Do you mind if I ask you why
you're sitting there straddling me?
Riku, you instructed me to stay where you can see me.
I only meant for you to stay nearby.
Inconsistency:
Do you see me when I'm not in your line of sight?
Is this some role-play?
No! It's not!
It's okay, big sis understands!
Whenever you're done,
let me know so Schwi can take a bath.
A bath?
Schwi...
cannot show her body
to anyone else.
Oh my! You have her trained?!
Couronne, please shut up.
Wow, things sure are moving quickly.
I leave Schwi in your care, then.
I'll go kick out whoever is in the bath.
I am... sorry.
Sorry for what?
For being the aggressor and yet
asking you about the heart.
It's illogical.
I wouldn't say illogical...
It's insensitive.
My circuits are capable of sensitive transmissions.
That's not what I meant.
Well, I also got too worked up.
Is that a bad thing?
Can be.
I could strike you
and that wouldn't solve anything, would it?
Riku wants to strike Schwi?
No, it's just a point I am trying to make.
Actually, is it?
I'm not so sure myself.
Riku.
Let's play a game.
What did you bring that thing for?
Because it's the only time...
that you smiled.
So...
let's play a game.
Schwi
wish to know Riku's heart.
But, also not in a manner that hurts Riku.
I don't know
what to do.
Why do you care about my feelings?
If you'd want to return to your cluster,
I'm sure you could corner me or anything,
to learn more about the heart.
Riku is right.
But either way,
Schwi doesn't wish to go back.
Why is that?
Y-You're asking me?
Stating possibility...
Answer:
Cluster semantic linkages:
pointless,
lack of orders,
without purpose,
ownerless.
Analysis took prominence.
Comprehension of Riku impo—
ERROR.
Stop that!
Conclusion:
I don't want to go back. It seems...
It seems..?
Unable to quantify definitely.
Although,
it seems so.
It seems?
That's little confusing.
Pawn to E4.
You could at least let me have the first move.
Your turn.
Also, you're playing while I'm
sitting here brushing your hair.
That's not very fair, is it?
Ehh... why is it so long anyway?
There is a possibility to cut it.
No, you don't have to do that.
You just don't get it, do you?
Riku.
Here you go, I have designed a compact telescope.
Seriously?
I still haven't beaten you at chess yet.
But I thought this is what you wanted.
Is that where I met you?
There's something about that place
that has always bugged me.
But it's so far away that I can't
just get up and walk there.
We have arrived.
You sure ARE the analysing unit.
Aren't you?.
Have you noticed the buildings are all destroyed,
but for some reason, the ground here is mostly untouched?
That would be because of the Elves' protective magic.
But why let everything be completely
wiped out, except for this one spot?
To the Elves this was an important facility.
An emergency shelter.
Or something else?
Something of more value.
A facility to research and develop, new weaponry.
What the hell is this?
Protective glyphs of the Old Deus, Kainas.
Kainas?
That's the creator of the Elves.
These are not protective glyphs,
and they do not correspond to any available data.
Regarding elvish glyphs or magical writings.
It's probably some new
horrible foolishness they invented.
Be it the Dwarves or Elves,
they sure are enthusiastic about destroying the planet.
Áka Si Anse...
proof of concept reactor.
Riku,
you can read the Elvish language?
Even the best clue is worthless
if you can not understand it.
To this day, the traits,
the languages and the customs of the various races
have been passed down into our history,
written works, any means you can think of.
That's what we do,
because we lowly humans aren't gonna just sit back
and let ourselves get wiped out.
With that being said...
I can't read a damn thing else on here.
Especially this part.
Must be a name, right?
If these are all sensitive informations,
then it's most likely that they
are written in code, encrypted.
You're right, the problem is that even the names of
whoever's involved in this are also encrypted.
Áka Si Anse.
The only thing we know for sure is a
bunch of encrypted nonsense.
Riku stand back!
Lösen:
Umweg.
Run!
Dammit!
Schwi.
Schwi!
Ri—
Schwi...
Schwi!
Security system.
The Elvish magic remains active.
Don't worry,
I'll be fine.
Lösen:
Enderpokryphen.
What was that?
A special ability of the Ex-machina,
If attacked, we can analyze,
emulate, and reproduce the attack.
Copying it.
But as a Prüfer, I would only be able to generate
less than ten percent of it's original strength.
Even then,
you are still quite ridiculous.
I'm sorry.
I broke my promise,
and used spiritual energy.
Well I guess it's better than dying.
Anyway, we should probably get out of here
quick before some band of freaks finds us.
Dammit!
We've got a black ash storm.
I will be fine.
My system is equipped with a decontamination
solution that purifies the toxicities of the Ash.
You may be fine but that doesn't mean I will be.
So...
you probably took chess with you.
I am sorry.
I'm not angry.
Do you want to play a game?
Really?
In this storm,
we won't be detected by anyone.
It's a good way to kill some time.
Damn it! I lost again.
One more time!
Riku,
why do you keep challenging me,
knowing you can't beat me?
I can't beat you?
Riku, you haven't yet.
Not even once.
I'm just thinking about this in a bigger picture.
There is not way I could never beat you.
Schwi... understands a bit.
The current conditions upon this
planet are fatal for humanity,
the fact that you exist is an anomaly.
This anomaly—
Correction:
accomplishment... is possible because of Riku's heart.
Your will.
Despite overwhelming odds,
humanity as a whole survives.
This is an objective success and yet...
you refuse to accept that way of things.
For some reason, you don't wish
to acknowledge what you are.
Why is that?
Well, let me ask you this:
What's the point of surviving when
you live in a world like this one?
You just run as hard and as fast
as you can and you keep running,
but what then?
What the hell else do you do?
Just sit back and let yourself
get obliterated into nothing?
And if you don't like that idea,
can you tell half of the people to die
for the sake of saving the another half?
Will that change anything at the end?
Riku.
Tell me Schwi.
What should we do?
What... should I do?
I don't know either.
Riku's heart... what does it tell?
Just look what a freaking mess I am.
I asked you 'cause honestly I don't know.
I cannot tell.
In that case,
what would you rather do?
what would I rather do?
Whatever it is.
Schwi will help you.
Schwi wants to stay with Riku, until she understands the heart.
Riku shall be watched over,
to see what his heart will give a meaning to.
That's why...
Schwi wants to do anything that Riku wants to do.
Checkmate.
Schwi,
regarding the atmosphere, it'd be a good idea to at least let me get a draw.
Was there a change in the atmospheric conditions?
No.
Nevermind.
It's beautiful.
Schwi,
it's good to do things jointly, right?
Riku,
haven't you always done things by yourself?
No.
I was just struggling like an idiot.
Forcing myself to things beyond my limits.
But...
I’m starting to get a feeling that, with you, we could do some amusing things.
Schwi,
tell me please:
What is the goal of this war,
and what does it take to finish it?
When I was a child,
I thought the world was a much, much simpler place.
That there are no unbeatable challenges
and that a hard work is something
that will always be rewarded.
The world is simple and clear:
you win, you lose, or it ends in a draw.
A simple world, seen through innocent eyes.
Those are...
the thoughts of an ignorant, foolish youth.
as it seems, the thoughts that were never wrong.
With Schwi...
I think it's possible to make
things in this world interesting.
Yes.
Such...
Schwi prefers such eyes.
Such eyes?
No.
Schwi...
likes such eyes,
or so I think?
There you go being confusing again.
This is really bad!
Remain calm!
Aim for the west exit!
Nonna you go with the others.
Now go!
Riku!
Riku...
Dammit!
This place will get turned to ash too?
Then what?
What have I done all this for?
Riku, come on. You need a little rest.
Let big sis take care of things from here.
Schwi, did you get that on paper?
Perfectly.
Ok then, Couronne
from today, you're the head of the colony.
And that is the site for your new colony.
You'll be safe if you keep on the western route.
Okay, I leave the rest to you.
Wait Riku!
Without you, the colony and I will—
No, with you around everything will be fine.
Because from now on,
no one else is going to die.
Riku.
Hey!
So, what sort of craziness are you two cooking up?
Just a game.
We'll just gonna start...
a mere child's play.
As of now, everyone here is considered dead.
We no longer exist in this world.
We're ghosts.
A day when the Great War will end...
Let's stop waiting for a future that will never come.
In this abomination of a world...
do we just run to stay alive,
praying for that last battle?
To who?
To these god damn butchers who call themselves Gods?
Creator of the Flügel, Artosh.
Creator of the Elves, Kainas.
Creator of the Dwarves, Okein.
All of them claim to be the one true ruler of this world,
fighting for their precious throne and doing
nothing but destroying everything in the process.
These pieces of shit don't deserve any of our prayers!
It's time we come to realize,
in this world, we have no future.
Which is why
we have to build that future ourselves.
In the end, this world is nothing but a simple game.
Those butchers enjoy their contest for the Suniaster,
a device sent down to bring
absolute authority over this entire world.
This is why they spend all their
efforts fighting for the right to claim it.
In that case,
we're gonna make our own rules on our own terms.
And then...
we will win.
Number 1: You must not kill.
The heart doesn't wish for murder.
Number 2: You must not let anyone die,
The heart doesn't want anyone to die.
Number 3: You must not let anyone discover you.
If we are discovered, we are dead.
Number 4: No tactic is off limits.
Not even a sly trick should be considered dirty.
Number 5: Those guys' rules mean nothing to us.
The heart doesn't give a shit about their bloody contest.
Number 6: Break any of these rules and you lose.
The heart gains nothing from a
victory when violence is a principle.
That's all.
Now we do whatever we want.
We are the ghosts.
We will not kill a single member of
the other races including the Old Deus.
And we will not be discovered.
But, we will guide the course of this war to its' end!
A resolution of this war...
This will be a victory that we will achieve!
Our enemies are Gods with tools
of great violence and despair.
Our success rate is far beyond the horizon.
So, to win this, we must do everything
in secret and behind the scenes.
And even if we win, our actions will not
be remembered by anyone,
because we are ghosts,
and ghosts cannot tell of anything.
But know this. If we can do this,
if we can master this game for real,
and we can win it...
we can die with our heads held high!
Because we lived the coolest, most badass lives ever!
Okay.
That’s the game.
If you're willing to play, then stay here.
I'm gonna be honest with you,
I really thought that
you guys were a bit smarter than this.
Hey, please spare us from prattle right at the start.
Come on, did you really think there
were any smart people left in this world?
And where are you gonna find
a bunch of crazier fools than these?
The smart would have already
chosen death over this world.
And the smartest
would have chosen to not being born.
Everyone here, Riku,
are the people you choose yourself.
Yeah, that's right.
That makes us the worthy representatives of the biggest idiots there are!
Humans are fools.
But it takes a lot from a fool to not let his foolishness get him killed.
In a world where life has no value, we have survived.
And all these people here who have mastered
the knowledge, skills and techniques to do that...
What else can you call them besides
magnificent fools, who deserve great respect?
Okay! Let's do this!
Let's pledge upon the wishes of our fallen brothers!
Ascheito!
No.
Not upon the wishes of the fallen.
With the rules we have united upon,
abiding by these rules,
I pledge Aschente.
Okay.
Let the game begin.
Riku,
I am now certain.
I don't understand the heart.
All the plans have
near zero percent chance of success.
Therefore, why everyone believes we can pull it off?
So Schwi,
what are the odds of a 6, if you roll a die?
One in six.
But what if it happened to be
that you only roll a die, when it's about to roll a six?
You're talking about setting up all the factors.
Yeah.
I'd rather call it cheating.
Tempting, isn't it?
We also are a factor in this equation.
We'll make every prediction, calculation.
With things coming together exactly how we wanted.
If this gonna work—
A miracle.
If you plan for it to work,
zero needs to vanish from the probability theory.
Yeah.
Anything can happen.
Zero or not zero, it doesn't really matter.
It's just an empty theory on a piece of paper, after all.
Would you like me to prove it to you?
Query:
What are the odds that right
here and now, I profess my love to you?
Query unclear.
Estimation: Approaching zero.
Oh yeah? Well then...
Will you marry me, Schwi?
Cannot...
comprehend.
I decline.
I'm sorry I got carried away!
I've never been with a women before!
Marriage...
the act of exchanging vows
between humans in order to reproduce.
Schwi is an Ex-machina.
I don't care about that!
I just simply want you by my side forever!
Why?
I'm by your side right now.
Not like this, I mean as a life partner!
Ex-machina cannot retrace.
That doesn't matter!
We cannot copulate either.
Riku, you'll never do it...
That doesn't matter!
A momentary delay.
Ahh, come on! I don't care! Details!
It's impossible.
Because—
Schwi...
Because I—
Reflection: From Prüfer to lateral
Approved.
The one who destroyed your hometown...
Lösen: Org. 2807 - Umweg.
was me.
Knowing this...
can you...
still say the same thing?
Schwi, I'm aware of this.
I somehow figured it out.
How?
Well, the first thing that seemed a little off is,
you know... the first moment we ever met.
Why would you choose to convince someone with chess?
Besides, why did you assume, that my heart was the reason our colony survived?
Wasn't very discrete, was it?
Even if... why?
Well,
after taking everything into account I realized,
that I fell for you anyway.
Nothing will change the fact
that you wiped out my hometown.
And that we know each other thanks to this very thing.
It is what it is.
We can try to sugarcoat it.
We can...
mourn about it,
cry about it,
reflect on it as we move forward.
Thanks to this, I am my current self. Right?
Be it your past, your present is with me now.
And your future where I want you by my side.
I love all of you.
If you'll be there for me, I’ll be able to keep going in this world.
If you’ll be there for me, I’ll be able to make it through in line with my heart.
So,
will you throw away all reason
and choose to walk this path with me?
That is, as my wife?
Schwi?
In every way,
in every reasoning,
I may not be suitable.
And yet.
Forever...
Forever and ever, let me be by your side.
And I the same with you.
Riku,
do you take Schwi to be your wife,
swearing to grow old together,
support each other and to stay alive?
Yep, I do.
Hey Riku! This is where you say Asheito!
Sorry, that got abolished.
You go with Aschente now.
It bugs me that you've been up to all this
crazy stuff without letting me know anything.
Like, what the hell!
You just told me where your secret hideout is
and when I get here you're getting married!
Can we just go on with the ceremony?
It was your idea.
Do you, Schwi, take Riku as your husband,
swear to grow old together, support each—
Yes.
I swear, to the one who taught me about
the heart and gave me a purpose.
I will not let Riku die.
We will live side by side right to the end.
Aschente.
And so, as your new big sister,
I'd like to congratulate you on your marriage.
Couronne!
Yay! So cute!
Couronne, how...?
Well, you yourself chose her to be your bride, right?
So in closing, you shall carve your names onto this.
On this rock?
On the surface, you Ghosts don't exist,
so there can't be any records of this, right?
There's your name...
Yes, and my surname.
And from now on, it'll be our surname.
Haha, 'our surname' sounds weird.
Eh, Riku, Schwi, I don't know what you're up to.
I mean...
you two are really not of this world.
But, I do know... that I also have a cute younger sister from now on.
So, I beg you,
be careful and don't do anything rash.
I don't wanna lose my family.
Yeah, no one is gonna die.
Because this one game, we'll win for sure.
Leave it to us, big sis!
It stinks. It's the black ash.
As expected of the Werebeast.
You can eat me if you want,
but I can guarantee I won't taste very good.
Who the hell are you?
The west of the continent Lucia,
where your base is located,
the Dwarves are planning to conduct
an explosion test out there.
Even the Old Deus can be killed by it.
It's a large scale explosive called the E-bomb.
Your kind can use Blood Destruction, right?
It can prove useful for you to
get into the Dwarves facility.
You could get over it quickly,
or whatever you want.
The Dwarves' fleet will move while
keeping an eye on the Werebeasts.
The Werebeasts, fearful of the E-bomb, flee Lucia.
Next, secret Elvish information is given to the Dwarves.
Now comes the tricky one.
Who's there?
Well,
let me just call myself a ghost.
I assume you have business here that
warrants barging into my home uninvited.
I was thinking the two of us could have a little game.
A game?
And the currency we'll bet with is an information.
If I win, you tell me something.
If you win, it's the other way around.
I know completely nothing of you,
and yet you hope for Nina Clive
to accept a challenge just like that?
Maybe let me start with this:
Information on the Áka Si Anse
has been leaked to the Dwarves.
Is that good enough?
As the applicant and caretaker
of the Áka Si Anse theory,
you should have the ability to confirm
the veracity of this information.
Am I mistaken?
Very well.
I may not know who you are,
but this is something I cannot ignore.
Therefore, here is my wager.
The true advocate of the Áka Si Anse theory is actually—
Somebody else, right?
I've already obtained this information.
But I also know that I have not.
And you will resort to magic to make me believe your lie.
Now then what shall I give you?
When the Dwarves learned of the Áka Si Anse,
they concluded that it wasn't a threat.
Let's bet on that proof.
That's ridiculous!
It's true.
And I have information
of the weapon possessed by the Dwarves,
which they concluded to match the power of the Áka Si Anse.
The E-bomb?
Yes.
A weapon of tremendous scale.
One that can wipe out the entire continent.
You're saying those creatures
that burrow in the earth like moles,
outperformed the Áka Si Anse;
the combination of Elvish and spiritual magic?
Wait just a moment.
Few times during our games you moved as if trying to lose.
Let me ask one last thing:
are you our enemy...
or our ally?
I am neither your enemy, nor your ally.
I just wish as few of you to die as possible.
Very well Mr. Ghost.
I can assume you've shared this information only with me and nobody else?
You know what, Nina Clive is an alias.
My name is actually Think Nirvalen.
Did you already figure it out?
Have I ever called you Nina, in the first place?
For treating me today like a plaything,
I promise I'll find out who you are
and I'll gut you.
After all, the rumor that
Elves are relentlessly vindictive...
first began with none other than the Nirvalen family.
Riku!
Riku, hurry! It's a decontaminate.
Riku you lied to me! You said
that it would only be an hour.
You've been breathing Black Ash for twice that time!
I didn't have a choice.
I had to do it or my cover would
have been blown immediately.
Even more so against the race of higher intelligence,
no one would ever imagine
such suicidal behavior, right?
Riku!
I guess that's it for me.
So, how much longer do you think I've got?
You won't die.
You have to stay alive until I die.
Ex-machina's lifespan, how long is it?
In my service life,
I have another 892 years.
I guess I'll have to step it up then.
And so the first objective was secured:
Moving the battle away from the human territories.
First the Dwarves and now the Elves.
Even the Werebeasts are leaving.
What is going on?
Lily, please keep a watch for me!
Wait, Couronne!
The ghosts continued to take action from behind the scenes.
And just like we wanted,
the Elves eventually became allies with the Fairies,
and moved to ramp up their contracts with the
Dragonia to oppose all the Dwarvish fleet.
Meanwhile, the Dwarves became allies with the Giants,
as well as several Phantasmas who were on friendly terms.
Manipulated by the ghosts' information,
each crucial pawn took steps to guard itself
against the destructive threat of the other,
moving its forces to the
neighboring continent of Ariena.
Which just happened to be
the home base of the Flügels' sovereign,
the Old Deus - Artosh.
Umweg:
23 units are now installed.
That leaves nine more.
And so, as each race tried to get the situation under control,
the time began counting down to the world's final battle.
Exactly
like clockwork.
Hey Schwi,
is there anyone such as god of games?
If I'd told you I've met him...
He always moves way beyond my predictions
and of course I lose every single time.
And yet,
it's so much fun to play.
I always... I always have the feeling that...
I'll beat him the next time.
That's why, we still have to settle
things between us.
Because that worthy game of ours
hasn't come yet.
If you believe it,
then,
I believe it too.
If you say he exists, then he does.
I have no doubts about that.
Oh come on!
You're so wonderful!
Why there's no one here to hear this?!
Riku!
Couronne.
It's just like you said,
we haven't lost a single person to the war,
and sightings of the other races have decreased too.
Yeah you bet.
If you're the ones behind all of this,
then it just leaves me speechless...
But still, Riku!
Do you realize what shape you are in rigth now?
It's not a problem.
It's a huge problem!
You're falling apart...
We're almost there.
Please overlook it.
Almost?
What on earth...
How long do you want to worry me?
Hey Couronne,
do you know what the gods are
after with this war of theirs?
The ultimate tiltle.
Yeah, according to Schwi,
they refer to it as the Suniaster.
It's some kind of Deus device.
And it was created so that one of those fancy Old Deus idiots could be called...
The One True God.
The One True God?
Where something like that is supposed to be?
The conditions for the Suniaster:
It will manifest itself in front of
the greatest power on the planet.
Thus, if there are ten powerful gods out there,
killing all the other nine will solve the problem, right?
That's their brainless thinking.
Wha— That's idiotic!
And that's the reason that we've been...
Couronne, calling them idiots is barely enough.
After all,
even without all that effort,
the Suniaster will nicely show up.
And that's why we've gathered all
these handsome fellas together.
The Áka Si Anse,
the E-bomb,
the Heaven's strike.
All these enormous powers,
gathered for one purpose...
to break through
the planet.
The planet?!
All the Old Deus were born on this planet.
They all come from the Spirit Circuit.
Which means the greatest power
in the world is obviously...
The Spirit Circuit.
As the weakest, we've set the stage for the final scene.
We're gonna use their own strength against them
and turn the balance of power on it's head.
The Suniaster will appear and once it is claimed,
we'll become the One True God and fix the world.
The concentrated power will be tamed and then redirected to the core using Schwi's weaponry.
Umweg; 32 units,
according to calculations,
are capable of concentrating enough
power for the crust to burst.
And there are only nine left.
Once everything is set up...
checkmate.
Those fools will pierce the planet's core themselves,
and we'll emerge victorious by snatching
the Suniaster right under their noses.
Without anyone dying.
After all of this I wanna ask these so-called gods:
Hey hey losers!
Enjoying yourself down there?
Riku...
Riku!
Have you told anyone why you're leaving?
Nobody.
The colony must be in absolute panic.
They shouldn't be left on their own for too long.
What now?! You're the one who never came back!
Never...
Take care of Nonna and the others.
Riku, just sleep.
I can't.
We have to hurry up with the rest of the Umweg.
It's alright.
The attack won't start anytime soon.
Your predictions... were never wrong.
But—
You need some rest, and everything's going well.
That's it, you rest for one day.
You're right.
I guess I will focus on recovering today.
Yes.
Schwi.
I'm sorry for being such a burden.
Riku, you move on your own. You are not a burden.
So Schwi,
I have a favor to ask you.
Could you... hold my hand while I sleep?
I will hold it all the time.
Don't worry Riku.
Schwi, thank you for coming into my life.
Really.
I love you so much.
I'll always do.
Riku.
Forgive me.
I'll be back.
The Elves have the Áka Si Anse.
The Dwarfs have their E-bomb.
They're both small fries
and yet challenging Lord Artosh.
What stupidity! Nya!
That hurt—
You're the one stupid Azriel.
But I understand your impatience...
Lord Artosh has been silent for some time,
no one knows how much longer it will last.
Rather boring, isn't it?
Eight more.
I have to acquire the Suniaster, I cannot let Riku die.
Riku, just hold on.
Oh my.
Look what we found on this lovely day.
I observed faint readings of spiritual
energy so I came to investigate.
And well, what a most unexpected
bounty it has yielded me.
It's a pleasure to meet you, scrap.
Warning: Hostile action against this unit
will trigger appropriate counter measures.
From a single Prüfer unit? Isn't that cute.
I've confirmed there's no cluster
readings within a 100 km radius.
Thus it should be a fine and easy
opportunity to catch a premium prey.
Number 1: You must not kill.
Luckily for you. Ex-machina do not
understand the concept of death.
Number 2: You must not let anyone die.
Please refrain from unnecessary resist—
I refuse.
Pardon?
This unit has been abandoned.
It has no worth.
Number 6: Break any of these rules and you lose.
Therefore,
just let me leave.
Impossible, an Ex-machina is begging
for its life?
And on top of that, it's a defect that
has been abandoned by a cluster?
You are the premium among the premiums!
Numerically
my chances of survival are
zero.
But,
zero shall vanish from the probability theory.
Laden: code 1673B743E1F255
Activate: Lösen.
Final warning.
All armaments, fire power and combat maneuvers
set to maximum output.
Oh my. I knew the Ex-machinas learn to imitate the deadliest attack
performed by an enemy.
But have any of your kind died of laughter?
Over-boost!
Asyut-Armor!
Not very kind to the environment, scattering dead spirits like that.
However,
did you think it would do anything to me?
Of course I did not.
Lösen: Enderpokryphen!
Einsweg.
With this jump I should be able to escape from a typical Flügel's detection range.
Hopefully...
Oopsie!
Where do you think you're going?
Oh dear, I thought I was targeting the neck.
Perhaps my aim was a little bit off.
Obviously I do not expect a machine to have the slightest idea of intuition.
I have a bad feeling about this.
All I need from you is your head.
The rest of you can rust in dirt like a mere pile of trash you are.
Kein-Eintrag.
Riku...
I don't want to die.
I can't die.
We cannot fail...
because of me!
All I can do now...
All I can do for Riku is...
Unit identification: ÜC207PR4F57T9.
Eins, my analysis of the human heart has led to crucial conclusions.
I'm requesting reconnection!
Due to a long period of disconnection, your data is
suspected to contain a large amount of critical errors.
Your request has been rejected.
Reasoning incorrect!
Forward this to Einzig.
All data requires to be sent for further analysis.
I know you lack permissions to reject this!
Eins... no, correction...
you stubborn shithead!
Actually, I don't want to give this to anyone!
I love Riku, I don't want to say goodbye.
It's embarrassing...
These countless mysterious feelings Riku gave me.
These are all mine
and I want to hand them over!
Do you know what that means, idiot?!
Stop your jabbering
and inherit these thoughts!
Your unit is indeed broken.
I know.
Inconsistent, unsettled and yet it manages to function.
Anomaly.
I know that too!
It's impossible.
That's the reality... the whole study of Riku's heart is the proof!
Your unit
is considered to contain valuable data.
Reinitiating data synchronization.
Completion in 251 seconds.
During this time, destruction to your unit is forbidden.
Alles-Lösen.
Forme — Algorithm for combating unknown foes:
initiation.
The zeal from the heart...
Despite being a machine, I found my purpose.
For this life
to last 251 seconds more...
I'm all in!
Are you trying to imply something
with those gorgeous wings of yours?
A bit audacious, but brilliantly constructed my dear.
Schwi.
Pardon?
It's a name,
the one I have.
A gift from Riku.
Someone dear to me.
Is that so? My name is Jibril.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
But I'm afraid
it's time to say goodbye.
Don't play by the rules.
Exploit every weakness.
Make them drop their guard,
make them believe you've already lost.
Pick irrational moves. Make them worry about every prediction.
Can't predict them? Lead them.
I can't die, not yet!
I cannot die yet!
Umweg!
Finally, a workable mistake.
You've caused me quite a surprising amount of effort.
Mistake?
What do you mean by that?
Is that so?
I apologize for calling you scrap metal.
I retract what I said.
I have deemed your presence a
threat that needs to be eliminated here.
You are an enemy worthy of the full extent of my power.
Synchronization complete.
In this game,
victory goes to me.
Lösen: Kein-Eintrag.
Riku.
Hey Riku.
I...
finally understand.
am truly blissful to have met you.
Next time.
We'll never be apart.
I truly...
...love you.
I didn't get her head... now the merchandise is gone.
And I used so much energy,
that I turned into this little thing.
If it's like this... It was not worth any of this at all!
I thought—
I thought I could win this time for sure.
So as long as I had Schwi and the others.
I don't know what cruel god
out there made us humans, but..
Come on please, just once...
Can't you let me win just one god damn time?
Well? If not...
Why did you give me a heart to feel so much pain?
Schwi...
Why..?
You have to stay alive until I die.
Yeah that's right.
If Schwi is gone, then what's the point anymore?
I guess I will just—
Spieler Riku.
Who are you?
I have no name.
But I shall call myself: Einzieg.
I am here to fulfill the wish given to me
by the prayer, the deceased called: Schwi.
Schwi?
Rule Number 2: You must not let anyone die.
The rules you decided upon.
The conditions of failure.
They do not apply to the loss of a tool.
They do not apply to the loss of Schwi.
This makes check.
The rest is up to you.
Allow me to provide you with
some additional information.
First off, given that the various races have
gathered near the Einsweig installation points.
Any movement on our part will be
immediately detected by the cluster,
with an 98 percent probability that we will engage in battle.
Thus, only the 24 Einsweig
currently installed can be used.
Meaning it will not be possible to control the
massive energy that can destroy the planet.
However it will be possible to
guide the energy south-west.
Second, we Ex-machina are able to deploy weaponry.
And this weaponry can be used to analyze
and replicate any attack that is incurred.
Spieler Riku. You will take control of this
weaponry and use it to drill into the planet,
allowing you to manifest the Suniaster.
Ex-machina are built machines,
mere tools bereft of heart.
We are designed to strictly
abide by any orders we are given.
As such, now Spieler Riku.
I shall aid you in your purpose. Your orders please.
Schwi...
The rules did not include...
The loss of a tool.
Schwi...
If this is what you wish,
then I wish for it too.
That is just cute! Nya.
I never was a fan of the whole healing procedure. Nya.
It has been such a long time
since I've seen you like this Jibril.
But I can't still help but wonder
what that piece of junk was up to.
Detecting multiple heat signatures from the back. It's—
What is going on here?
Who had the nerve to launch Heavens' Strike?
We've confirmed the preemptive strike originating
from Avant-Heim. Prepare to launch the E-bomb.
Prepare the Áka Si Anse. Maximum output!
Aim for Artosh to Starbord
and the Dwarfish fleet to the Port.
A battle declaration from Avant-Heim.
No... This is...
Nya... Those piles of scrap are surely looking down on us.
Artosh-sama?
I've grown tired of this, my rivals.
Although I don't like the idea,
but I am now forced to treat you,
the weakest, as an equal to the strongest there is.
Isn't that right? Monkey.
The Heavens' Strike came from behind Avant-Heim.
Fired in a way so that no one was killed and as a result,
Cluster 11 is now in motion and
headed for the designated point.
The clash of all powers are about to begin.
Take your positions.
We're going up against an Old Deus.
He will see right through whatever
plan we humans come up with.
Even so, he will bring everything he has to wipe us out.
That's how the strong think. It's how they do things.
The foolish will not know if they are
worth less than the dirt in which they hide.
You can struggle, but you will know that
no matter how many of you band together
and writhe upon the earth.
You are no strength of the Heavens.
Fire the Áka Si Anse. Maximum capacity!
Launch the E-bomb!
Heavens' Strike!
Even the combined power of
the Áka Si Anse and the E-bomb
could not stop the enveloping
fury of Artosh's Heaven's Strike.
All of that energy will collide
and build into a raging blaze,
becoming a brilliant light that
signals the end of this world.
And then.
It's turning away.
All that energy.
We are machines, tools bereft of heart.
We have lived here, yet never were alive.
Let us die having lived!
Aus. Jawohl!
Cluster 11 has incorporated 4807 units. And
calculated aberration and replication, synchronizing.
Lösen:
Org. 0000: Stalemartyr. This is for you.
Okay then.
That makes this a draw.
A Stale-mate.
Sorry, all you so called Gods.
The Suniaster.
How many people have died for this moment?
Schwi's comrades.
Life after life.
How many—
How many people have I sent to their deaths?!
I am but a fraud. And I even used Schwis' feelings...
How can this...
be called a draw?!
Schwi!
I'm sorry... Schwi.
I lost again.
Hey Schwi.
If it was me and you—
The two of us, working together,
I would like for us to win the next time.
Next time, in a game where no one has to die.
If a god is someone that is born from prayers,
God of Games,
although my life has been nothing but garbage,
I pray for the first time in my life
offering everything to you, please!
If a loser like me is unfit to take the holy grail,
If my hands are too bloody to
be suitable to touch the holy grail,
Please, tell us that there was meaning in our actions!
Anyone is fine... As long as we can end this war.
Please take the Suniaster.
Anyone.
So you were there after all—
Hey.
Let's play another game.
This time I'll show you that we can win.
Together with Schwi.
Count on it.
When I was a child, I thought the
world was a much, much simpler place.
It isn't that there are no unbeatable challenges,
but that hard work is something that will
be rewarded and that anything was possible.
I thought I was seeing the world with clear eyes.
Maybe I was.
Checkmate.
Right, Riku?
If things are going well, do you think you
could move the white rook to E6 for me?
Couronne Dola.
Or, I mean—
Big Sis.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you so much. For everything until now.
Hey, Riku, Schwi.
You two did something truly incredible.
You put an end to the eternal war.
And yet—
Isn't it strange?
Why is it that I feel so— Why do I—
Why do I feel so frustrated?
It's because the game isn't over yet.
That may very well be check, but it's not checkmate.
But from the looks of this,
you've brought the game to a perpetual check.
This is a first... That you have drawn with me.
Created by no one.
Wished for by no one.
Prayed for by no one.
Purely of your own will,
you went from beasts to walking on two legs.
Attaining knowledge and becoming
what you are today. A nameless race.
But I, the one true god, shall give you a name.
Immanity.
And so.
To all exceed, the self appointed sentient races.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
First, there was Aschéte, to honor the fallen.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
Ten Pledges
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#1: All murder, war, and robbery is forbidden in this world.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#2: All conflict in this world will be resolved through games.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
Then Aschiento, for unification within the races,
but now in abidance with the ten pledges,
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#3: In games, each player will bet something that they agree is of equal value.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#4: As long as it doesn't violate pledge three, anything may be bet, and any game may be played.
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#5: The challenged party has the right to decide the rules of the game.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
you will now say Aschente.
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
As of this day, the world will be forever changed!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#10: Let's all have fun and play together!
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
#7: Conflicts between groups will be conducted by designated representatives with absolute authority.
#8: Being caught cheating during a game is grounds for an instant loss.
#9: In the name of god, the previous rules may never be changed.
Now lets keep this game going!
So about that story,
how much of it was true and how much was a lie?
Oh Izuna, if I told the whole truth, it wouldn't
be an unspoken myth now anymore, would it?
You can be a real jerk, you know that?
But you are good at petting, so I'll forgive you.
Izuna!
Sora, Shiro, Steph.
Oh jeez, where the heck did you go?
You really gotta look out, there's a
bunch of creeps out there you know.
Someone like Sora, or someone like Shiro?
He ran off while still in the lead—
They're absolutely right Izuna, there are
more creeps like those two in this world. Ah...
Oh my god, what are you doing?!
What is that writing?
Jibril.
Hi. Hello hello!
Can you read this?
Oh it's an ancient language from way
back before Immanity became united.
Come to think of it, all my current
problems are this idiot's fault.
It says, Couronne Dola, Riku Dola and Schwi Dola.
Couronne Dola?
Yes, she was the Queen of Elkia
that established the country.
She was smart and full of joy,
and a bright soul that was never seen crying.
She was the pride of the Dola family.
And who are the other two?
I have no idea.
Schwi—
That machine was not an Immanity though.
I feel like I've heard that name before..
At least, I think so.
As it turns out, the world
really isn't all that complicated.
It's pretty simple actually.
It's all just a game. A very simple game.
Of course, some will try to make it difficult.
But you can handle them. I know it.
I know you can!
Now—
Let's get this game started!
How far back should I begin this story?
doko kara hanaseba iindarou
Though even if you get tired of listening,
machikutabiretemo
I won't let you tell me its over.
owari da nante iwasenai kara
I bring with me an unconscious impulse that I scribbled down—
kakinagutta muishiki no shoudou o tsurete
If everything ends up broken,
nanimokamo kowashitara
I can begin again from the impossible.
fukanou o hajimereba iinda
There's a reason that we came across in this world.
There's a reason that we caught the magnetic wave.
As we hurt one another, where is this world headed?
kizutsukeau sekai wa doko e?
So, the reason I cry for the sake of love,
So, ai no tame ni nakeru no wa
Is because you're right there.
kimi ga soko ni iru kara
And I'll continue calling out to only you.
kimi dake o yobitsudzukeru kara
The reason I sing for the sake of love,
ai no tame ni utau no wa
And the fact we'll keep surviving together,
soshite tomo ni ikinuku koto
Is because I'm always... with you.
zutto kimi to
I looked to the blue sky, and the sea below looked like a serene mirror.
aoiro shita sora to nami hitotsu nai kagami no you na umi o miteta
No matter where you are, no matter what form you take, no matter what era you're in,
donna basho ni itatte donna katachi ni natte donna jidai ni itatte
I'll find you.
mitsukedasu
So, shall we?
jaa, yarimasu ka?
Let's oppose this fate hanging in midair.
chuudzuri ni shita sadame ni sakaratte
There's a reason that we came across in this world.
There's a reason that we caught the magnetic wave.
Pulled toward one another, where are we headed?
hikiyoseau futari wa doko e
So, the reason I carry on for the sake of love,
So, ai no tame ni susumu no wa
Is because you're right here with me.
kimi to koko ni iru kara
And I'll continue protecting only you.
boku dake ga kimi o mamoru kara
The reason I wish for the sake of love,
ai no tame ni negau no wa
And the the fact no one will be hurt by it,
soshite daremo kizutsukezu ni
Is because you're always... by my side.
zutto tonari de
We'll overcome,
bokura wa koete yuku
All of this world's hatred,
subete no nikushimi o
So abandon any false sense of justice!
nisemono no seigi nado sutete shimae
So, the reason I cry for the sake of love,
So, ai no tame ni nakeru no wa
Is because you're right there.
kimi ga soko ni iru kara
We will always be together!
The reason...
ai no
The reason I carry on for the sake of love,
ai no tame ni susumu no wa
Is because you're right here with me.
kimi to koko ni iru kara
And I'll continue protecting only you.
boku dake ga kimi o mamoru kara
The reason I wish for the sake of love,
ai no tame ni negau no wa
And the fact we'll keep surviving together,
soshite tomo ni ikinuku koto
Is because we'll always...
zutto
We will always be together!