When I was a child,
the world was simple for me.
Nothing was unbeatable
and hard work was always meant to be rewarded.
The world was clear:
you win, lose or it's a draw.
Better moves!
More efficient tactics!
I want a superior strategy!
Even if you lose this time,
you have another chance next time.
Stupid, ignorant brat.
That's how I thought.
A childish delusion,
a pathetic world of games.
The truth is
this world
is nothing like it.
It's coincidental,
unreasonable,
absurd,
and doesn't have any meaning.
Nevertheless...
Next time...
Next time for sure...
Elkia
Why?
Why can't I win?!
Not to brag, but I've only lost once in my entire life.
The sixth of the ten pledges:
#6: Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
"Any bets made in accordance with the pledges must be upheld."
One of the absolute laws laid down by the One True God.
I'll crush you...
Next time I'll definitely crush you!
Next time, huh?
If you couldn’t beat them, you don’t stand a chance against me.
Sora and Shiro? You know them?
Alright, during the next game I'll tell you an interesting story.
For the snack I just got.
You just want to distract me, please.
Do whatever you want, please.
Great! Let's get into it!
It's an ancient myth that no one has ever heard before.
Not listening, please.
So...
this story happened over six thousand years ago.
The earth and sky were then ravaged by a cruel war.
As time passes, no one remembers it anymore.
And yet,
it's a story I will never forget.
It's a big one.
Black ash is falling, hurry up.
Ivan?
It's okay.
How's the compass?
Too much black dust around.
We need to rely on our senses.
Don't let your guard down.
Riku!
Come quick! There's a—
That's...
A Dwarven world map! And it's very recent!
That's not all.
It shows the distribution of all forces. Even the Dwarves' strategy.
Ivan, Aley,
compare it to ours, make corrections.
I'll take care of this one.
Aschieto!
A message... from the Dwarves?
Fusion...
detonation?
How much of this world do they plan to destroy?!
We're outta here!
Aley, it uses spiritual energy. Leave it.
But—!
You wanna die, just say so.
Fuck!
Ivan,
this is an order.
Die here.
Aschieto.
Ivan!
Take care of my kid.
Too bad, Riku.
The bait is here! Get me Demonia!
They say there used to be something called "the sun".
It lit up the sky,
turning all of it blue.
A fairy tale
to lift people's spirits.
Gods and their creations
burned the earth, choking the heavens with soot and raining down the ashes of dead spirits.
Riku!
These ashes...
are the most merciful option,
I guess.
No-n-na!
Here.
Whoa! That's my name? It says Nonna?
I want one too, Couronne!
I was first!
Sure,
one at a time.
Couronne! They're back.
Riku!
Riku, thank goodness.
Couronne...
Hey, you're late! You want to give me a heart attack?
Moreover, how many times have I told you to call me sis?
We tried to hurry.
About Ivan—
Riku!
Daddy!
Nonna!
Riku, Aley, welcome back! Where's daddy?
I want to show him the letter I wrote. Where's Daddy?
Listen to me, Nonna.
Riku...
Nonna,
your dad
won't be coming home.
W-why?
Because he died.
You're lying!
It's not a lie.
You're lying! Daddy promised me he'd come back!
Humans were supposed to win in the end!
We will win.
He sacrificed everything he could
so we could win.
That's not winning!
It should be you!
You're the one who should have died!
Nonna!
You two, go take a bath.
I'll clean myself up.
I said take a bath.
You guys stink!
So we could...
So we could win?!
Fucking hypocrite!
Ivan threw his life away!
I told him to die!
Say it!
I killed him, because that's the only way for us to live!
If that's how you stay alive,
what comes next?
How far I need to go?
Until I order half the village to bite the dust for the other half?
Or until I no longer give a fuck?!
When will this end?
How long will I have to
keep lying myself like this?!
Everyone born into this world
wants their life to mean anything.
Just like a reason to live,
the heart requires a meaning in death
to accept this reality.
Ivan's death won't be in vain.
Ruins of an elvish city,
things you almost never come across.
Staying sane in such a world...
could that really be called sanity?
The Dwarves?
No.
The scale of this destruction...
definitely the Flügels.
What a huge one...
My imagination?
Ex-machina?!
Examination.
Processing the circumstances.
Stay calm.
This thing always operates as part of a collective.
It shares consciousness with a cluster,
so others must be nearby.
That means—
Conclusion.
If I make any hostile moves,
all the Ex-machinas will see me as a threat.
I must not resist.
Onii-chan I cannot resist you.
Make a woman out of me.
Huh?
Error:
Cannot
comprehend.
I am the one who cannot comprehend!
Conjecture:
This scenario doesn't bring you satisfaction?
Something like this?
I'm not a weirdo who gets excited by you guys.
Query: Who are "you guys"?
Don't play dumb.
All of this gets sent to that cluster.
Negative.
This unit has been disengaged from the cluster.
Disengaged?
Are you alone?
Correct.
Then...
what does some stray Ex-machina want from someone like me?
May I even ask?
Response:
To analyze the unique fervor of humans.
The fervor of the heart.
The heart?
Reasoning:
Deeper investigation generated many logical errors, causing this unit to be disassociated.
Further observation has been conducted independently.
Observation, huh?
Are you planning to analyze the heart and then return with everything to that cluster?
Demand:
It is postulated that direct dermo-contact
leads to heart stimulation.
I request a procreation.
I refuse.
Adjustment:
You may take advantage of this unit in the village.
However, there's no orifice.
That's not the point!
Lösen:
Primary
game:
chess.
Request:
Participation in the game.
Conditions:
If this unit wins, it shall be taken to the colony and procreation shall occur.
Of all things, chess?
You guys are basically walking calculators.
But
what if...
I manage to win?
Answer:
You take this unit home
and permission for procreation shall be granted.
There's no difference!
Eh whatever, I guess there is no other way.
Let's play once.
Clarification:
You accept the game request?
Yeah, indeed.
Except I propose
much better win conditions for you.
We have arrived.
Hey, you seriously didn't use any spiritual energy for that?
Correct.
Utilizing spiritual energy would have saved 55.782 seconds.
Addendum:
This unit is an analysis model - Prüfer.
It's capabilities are less than other Ex-machinas'.
An absurd race like this waging a war?
No wonder the world has gone to hell.
What should I call you?
Cannot comprehend.
Your name. Do you have one?
Understood.
Identification number:
Übercluster 207 Prüfer 4F57T9.
That's your name?
Useless, we need to go with something easier.
Query:
This unit won, so it can analyze the human heart by staying with Riku.
Is this necessary for comprehension?
The heart isn't something that can be understood through words or procreation.
You'll need to stay with me for a while.
Query: Is self-naming allowed?
Sure, whatever.
Response:
Schwarzer.
Damn long and sounds weird.
We're taking Schwi.
Incoherence: Arbitrary parameter modified.
Can we do something with your talking?
Laden: Adopting personality 1610.
Onii-chan, is this better?
Never!
Retort: It was the result of high-cost computation.
Am I supposed to walk in there and say I have a sister out of nowhere?
Request: Provide optimal scenario.
Ok then, you're timid and don't talk too much.
It hurts a lot when someone asks about your past.
And quit starting every sentence sounding like a robot. Got it?
Understood.
Is this fine?
Are you... kidding?
Kidding?
I'm not.
I've chosen a personality with matching parameters.
Adaptiv emulation.
It'll do.
I want to always know where you are.
Is that clear?
And well, can you hide these tail-looking things?
I can't.
It's my power source. A quasi-nerve crossed with the Spirit Circuit.
Ehh, fine.
Let's say they're trinkets.
And one more time,
nobody can see that robot body of yours.
Okay.
Nobody can see it.
So cute!
Who is she?
Her colony got wiped out. I found her on the—
Is she...
your wife?
Wife?
Come on, don't be shy!
These days priority one is kids, two is food.
Three, four, five is more kids!
Can you stop that?
You stop too!
What does she mean?
She doesn't mean anything.
What's your name?
Schwi.
A lovely name.
How did you meet Riku?
We kissed...
and then a demand for procreation was made.
No, that's not—
Riku,
you couldn't wait...
at least until you return?!
You could have put it in a better way.
A better way?
Eh, whatever.
Anyway, can't you at least try to act more mature?
You make me look bad over here.
You don't like this form?
That's not my thing.
Then, what are you into?
Listen...
Do you even know what 'being into' means?
I want to know what encourages you.
That's not something I can tell you with words.
Remember what I told about the heart?
Then
let's play a game.
I refuse.
That was the only time.
I find games pointless and a waste of time.
What if it wasn't pointless?
I can bet
all the information you desire.
For example,
the reason behind the Great War
and what it takes to end it.
Give me a break.
As a mere human, I couldn't care less about it.
The only thing I need to know
is how to stay alive.
That's it.
That's why I brought you with me.
Ex Machina’s engineering tech, knowledge, maths
that's what I want if I win.
Okay.
Given
the state of the world...
The existence of humans in it is
an anomaly.
Logical reasoning
fails to explain it.
As a life form you are weak.
Your civilization is primitive.
You cannot utilize spiritual power, and yet
you resist.
There must be a reason,
a stimulus,
a factor.
I think that factor
resides
in the human heart.
That's what I want to—
Hey
Don't mock me.
Riku?
You slaughter us as you like.
You rob us of everything we have.
And what do you have to say?
"Hey humans, why do you guys still exist?"
"Let me see what's in your heart."
Yeah?!
You wanna know
what comes from my heart
since the very day I was born?!
Fuck every single one of you!
Do you know how many have died because of you?
How many you've killed?
How many—
How many you made me kill...
Riku, you're crying.
Therefore
I must have said something terrible
or hurtful.
Your heart
wants to kill me.
I see.
If you just
stab me here,
Schwi
dies.
Dies?
I am not alive…
A shutdown,
a permanent
termination.
Schwi wants to know your heart.
So now, that your heart desires it,
do you
kill Schwi?
Chad
Anton
Elmer
Cory
Dale
Siris
Ed
Darrell
Dave
Laks
Vin
Eric
Charlie
Riku?
Thomson
Shinta
Yann
Zaza
Zargo
Clay
Goro
Peter
Arthur
Morg
Kimmy
Datt
Ceril
Vigi
Volly
Ken
Savage
Leroy
Popo
Couthon
Lut
Shigure
Shao
Ulf
Balto
Asso
Kenwood
Peyl
Ahad
Hound
Balrof
Masashi
Memegan
Karim!
Ivan!
Forty-eight.
That's how many deaths I'm responsible for.
It's true that many more people have died due to the war
being swept away like dust,
but
these were the ones
I ordered to die.
Riku?
Are you awake?
I know you're tired, but maybe—
Oh! Sorry!
Might I inquire what you're sitting on me for?
Riku, I'm letting you know where I am.
You could have just stayed nearby.
Confusing...
You cannot see me when you sleep.
Intriguing role-play.
That's not it!
No worries, sis understands.
When you're done, Schwi can join us for a bath.
A bath?
Schwi
cannot show her body
to anyone else.
Oh my! Already this far?!
Couronne, please shut up.
Wow, you sure are moving quickly.
I leave Schwi in your care, then.
The bath will be all to yourselves.
I'm... sorry.
For what?
An aggressor asking a victim about the heart...
it's illogical.
Not illogical,
it's insensitive.
I have an abundant network of sensors.
That's not what I meant.
Well, I also got too worked up.
Is that a bad thing?
Yeah.
A desire to stab you wouldn't solve any actual problems.
Riku wants to stab Schwi...
It was just an example.
Or was it?
I'm not so sure myself.
Riku,
let's play a game.
What did you bring that for?
It's the only time
you open up...
so
let's play a game.
Schwi wishes to get to know your heart,
but not in a manner that harms you.
I don't know
what to do.
Why do you care about my feelings?
If you want to return to your cluster,
I'm sure you could force me to learn more about the heart.
You're right.
However, Schwi doesn’t care to come back.
Why is that?
Y-You're asking me?
Calculating line of reasoning.
Cluster semantic connections:
pointless,
lack of orders,
ownerless,
without purpose.
Motivation incomprehensible.
Adopting purpose impossible—
ERROR.
Stop that!
Conclusion:
I don't care to go back. Convergently...
Convergently?
Not determined definitively.
Although,
convergently.
Convergently?
That's little confusing.
Pawn E4.
Hey, at least let me have the center.
Your move.
Also, I'm sitting here brushing your hair.
That's not fair.
Ehh, it takes forever by the way.
There is a possibility to cut it.
No, there's no need.
Sometimes you really don’t grasp it.
Riku,
I designed a compact telescope.
Another thing? I haven't won at chess yet.
But you wanted it, I think.
Is that where we met?
Yeah...
One thing about this corner keeps bugging me.
In any case, it's too far to just go there on a whim.
We have arrived.
Quite enthusiastic unit, aren't you?
Have you noticed? All the buildings around have been destroyed,
but for some reason, this area is barely damaged.
Elven defensive magic...
But of all the possible places, why here?
For the Elves, it could have been an escape route,
a shelter,
or perhaps... even something more valuable.
A research facility for new weaponry.
What are these?
Protective glyphs of the Old Deus, Kainas.
Kainas?
Their creator?
Actually not protective.
The applied patterns, the technique
don't match any available data.
Must be some new crap they invented.
Just like the dwarves, they never really have enough power.
Áka Si Anse...
proof of concept reactor...
Riku, you can read Elvish?
Everything you sacrifice is worthless if you can't put things to use.
Legends, writings —
we've used every means you can think of.
Languages, customs, everything has been passed down to this day.
Despite the circumstances
we want much more than just to endlessly run away.
Either way...
I can't read a damn thing else here.
Especially this part.
Must be a name, right?
If it's classified elven information,
it's most likely encrypted.
That's right, it must be... that even the names of everyone involved are encrypted.
Áka Si Anse.
One thing we know for sure it's for no good.
Riku, stand back!
Lösen:
Umweg.
Run!
Shit!
Schwi.
Schwi!
Rik—
Schwi.
Schwi!
Schwi...
Security system...
Elf magic active...
But, I be fine.
Lösen:
Stehapokryphen.
What was that?
An ability of Ex-machina.
Received attack can be analyzed, adjusted, reproduced.
Copying it.
However, Prufer's analysis only allows for ten percent of the original power.
Even then,
that's still ridiculous.
I'm sorry.
I broke my promise
and used spiritual energy.
Well, it's better than dying.
Let's just get out of here quickly before any monster finds us.
Shit!
A black ash storm.
I will be fine.
I'm equipped with a decontaminant that neutralizes the toxicity of the ash.
Maybe you'll be okay, but I won't.
Well...
I bet you have chess with you.
I'm sorry.
I'm not picking on you.
Do you want to play a game?
Really?
In this storm,
we won’t be detected by anyone anyway.
We can kill some time with it.
Damn it! I lost again!
One more time!
Riku, if you can't win,
why do you keep playing?
I can't win?
Riku, you still haven't won
a single time.
I’ve managed to make you think longer.
Who said I can never win?
Schwi understands a bit.
Current conditions on the planet are fatal for humans.
Being alive is...
an anomaly.
This anomaly—
correction: achievement
is possible because of Riku's heart,
will.
Despite everything, humans survive.
An objective success.
And yet, you refuse to accept it.
You can't accept yourself.
Why?
Let me ask you,
what’s the point of surviving in this world?
You desperately run, escape,
and after that, what do you do?
What the hell can you do?
Just quietly hide until you're turned to dust?
And if not,
let's just throw away as many people's lives as needed?
That's the way to live, huh?!
Riku.
Tell me Schwi.
What can you do?
What... can I do...
I don't know either.
Riku's heart, what does it tell?
It's really pathetic of me.
I asked because I don't know myself.
I'm a mess...
Then what
do you want?
What do I want?
Whatever it is,
I will help you.
I'll stay by your side to witness the heart.
I'll stay to see what your heart will give meaning to.
Therefore...
Schwi wants what Riku wants.
Checkmate.
Schwi,
you could at least let me get a draw. Read the Atmosphere.
Should I measure the weather conditions?
No.
Nevermind.
Beautiful...
Schwi,
it's nice not to be alone.
Riku,
didn't you do everything alone?
No.
I struggled like a fool
putting up a front for myself.
But now...
I have a feeling that following what you want can be quite an idea.
Schwi,
tell me please,
what's the purpose of this war and what it takes to end it.
When I was a child,
the world was simple for me.
Nothing was unbeatable
and a hard work was always going to be rewarded.
The world was clear:
you win, lose or it's a draw.
A truly naive view of the world.
That was
the mindset of a stupid, ignorant brat.
actually the mindset of a doer.
Together
I think we can do some interesting things in this world.
Yes.
These...
These are good eyes.
Good eyes?
No.
Schwi
is into such eyes.
I think?
That's so like you.
This is bad!
Stay calm!
Go to the west exit!
Nonna, go with the others.
Run!
Riku!
Riku...
Damn it.
Everything turns to dust again?
What for...
What did we do all of this for?!
Riku, you need a break.
Let sister take care of things from here.
Schwi, did you write this down?
Completely.
Ok then, Couron.
From now on you are the leader.
This is the new colony location.
You'll be safe on the western route.
Okay, I leave the rest to you.
Wha— wait Riku!
Without you, the village and I will—
No, everything will be fine.
From this very moment,
nobody is gonna die.
Riku.
Hey!
What are you two cooking up, huh?!
Just a game.
We are...
going to start a mere child's play.
Everyone here is considered to have not escaped the village in time and to be dead.
We no longer exist in this world.
Ghosts.
"Someday the war will end."
Stop waiting for a future that will never come.
What do we do in this shitty world?
Run, hide and pray for mercy?
To who?!
To these butchers called gods?!
The creator of the Flügel, Artosh.
The creator of the Elves, Kainas.
The creator of the Dwarves, Okein.
Each of them claims the right to be the only god of this world.
Because of their pathetic quarrel they spread death and destruction!
These pieces of shit deserve nothing from us!
It's time to realize it.
In this world, we have no place.
That's why
we need to build it ourselves.
This world has become their game.
They fight for the Suniaster.
a conceptual device, which is said to grant absolute power over this world.
Their bloody contest is the only thing they care about!
In that case,
we'll also make the rules as we like
and then
go for victory.
1: You must not kill.
The heart despises murder.
2: You must not let anyone die.
The heart wishes no one death.
3: No one must discover you.
Being detected means death.
4: No trickery is off limits.
If you are not caught, no tactic is considered cheating.
5: Their rules mean nothing to us.
The heart despises their pathetic ways.
6: Break any of these rules and you lose.
The heart doesn't value a victory
that violates these rules.
That's all.
Nothing else restrains us.
We are ghosts.
Nobody, not even the Old Deus, will die by our hand.
And we'll stay in the shadows.
But, we will lead the course of this war to its end.
The end of the Great War!
That's the victory we will achieve!
Enemies are gods, ruthless destroyers with terrifying power.
Success is far beyond the horizon.
And since everything must be done in absolute secrecy,
even if we win, there will be no one to honor our deeds.
We are ghosts, ghosts don't exist.
But know this, if...
if we manage to finish this game,
to win it...
Living such a badass life,
I can die with no regrets!
Okay, that's the game.
Let only those who want to participate stay.
To be honest,
I thought you all were too sensible for this.
Oh, sorry that you overestimated us.
Riku, did you really think there are any sane people left?
Where would you find crazier fools than here in this world?
The wise would already choose death.
The wisest would choose not to be born.
Everyone here Riku,
are the ones you chose yourself.
Well said.
A truly elite representation of fools, isn't it?
It's human nature to be foolish.
And by not letting it kill you, you gain wisdom.
In a world full of terror, we've survived.
All those who put all their knowledge, skills and experience into it...
How can you call them if not the greatest masters of that foolishness?
Let’s do this!
Let's pledge on our grief for the fallen!
Ascheito!
No.
Not on the grief that has no end,
but on the values we stand for.
I pledge
Aschiento.
So,
let the game begin.
Riku,
now I completely
don't understand the heart.
These plans don't even exceed a 1% chance of success.
You don't get why we're so eager to do it?
So Schwi,
what's the chance of rolling a 6 on a die?
One sixth.
But what if
a certain unseen observer provides dice that only roll a six?
Acting as random factors…
Yeah.
This is our way to play.
Fun, isn't it?
Prudence fills each day of our lives.
Every risk, inaccuracy
will be taken by us into account.
If this succeeds…
A miracle.
I– In that case,
you need to reject probability theory.
True,
you must go beyond it.
No matter if it's 0 or 100.
It’s all just on paper.
Want me to prove it to you?
Query:
What are the odds that I'll confess my feelings right now?
Query unclear.
Answer: near zero.
You see?
Wrong.
Will you marry me, Schwi?
Cannot
comprehend.
I decline.
I'm sorry!
I thought it was that time already!
Mariage…
a contract between humans in order to reproduce.
Schwi is an Ex-machina…
Who cares about that!
I just want you forever by my side!
Why?
I’m by your side now.
Not like that! I mean as a life partner!
Ex-machina is unqualified.
Doesn't matter!
I cannot copulate either.
Riku, you'll never…
Doesn't matter!
A delay…
I said it’s nothing!
Impossible…
because–
Schwi…
Riku's–
Forwarding request to Einzig.
Approved.
Riku's village has been destroyed
Lösen: Org. 2807 - Umweg.
by Schwi.
Knowing this
can you
still say the same?
Schwi,
I'm aware of this.
I figured it out.
How?
Well… the first thing that was off
was when we first met.
Why convince someone with a game of chess?
Why wait for a specific person to be alone outside the village? And so on…
It really didn’t take a lot.
Even if… why?
Well,
the thing is that I love you
for every part of you.
The fact that you destroyed my home will never change,
and without it, we wouldn't be here right now.
It is how it is.
No point in running from it.
You cry,
weil,
gnash your teeth
and then, you move on to the next one.
That's what intrigued you about me,
isn't it?
Be it your past, your present by my side,
or your future shared with me,
I love them all.
With you, I want to keep going in this world.
With you, I'm able to live my life in line with my heart.
So…
will you leave all logic behind
and walk this path with me
as my wife?
Schwi…
It's clear
I'm a wrong choice
in so many ways…
And yet,
forever… and ever,
let me be by your side.
Allow me as well.
So Riku,
do you take Schwi as your wife
and vow to love her, support her, and stay alive?
Yeah, sure.
Come on! You say Ascheito!
Actually, I abolished it.
Now it's Aschiento.
You do all your things without letting me know.
It gets on my nerves.
Like, seriously!
You send me the location of your secret hideout,
and when I get there you're getting married?!
You insisted on the ceremony so much…
Can we move on?
So Schwi, do you take Riku as your husband,
and vow to love hi–
I do.
I vow to the one who gives me meaning, purpose, and the heart.
I won't let him die,
and till the end, will stay by his side.
Aschento.
Now, as your sister, let me congratulate you on your marriage.
Couron!
Yay! So cute!
Couron, how…
After all, it's you who chose her, isn't it?
So, to conclude, carve your names onto this.
On this rock?
You guys don't officially exist so you can't have any documents, right?
There's your name…
Yeah, and my surname.
It'll be our surname from now on.
Haha, it sounds weird, "our surname".
Hey, Riku, Schwi, you two…
I really have no idea what are you up to.
You two are beyond this world.
But… I do know
that I have a brother and a sister now.
So, please…
I don't want to lose another family.
Don't die on me.
Yeah, no one is gonna die.
This game, we've got in the bag.
Leave it to us, sis.
It stinks! The black ash!
You don't disappoint!
I wouldn't mind if you ate me
but I bet I wouldn't taste very good.
Who the hell are you?
The western coast of the continent Lucia, where you reside,
the Dwarves are planning a little experiment there…
Capable of killing an Old Deus
a massive hydrogen bomb.
You're a bloodbreaker, right?
Breaking into their facility shouldn’t be a problem.
You could handle it if you happen to care.
The Dwarf fleet regroups to avoid the Werebeasts.
The Werebeasts, fearful of the bomb, flee from Lucia.
Next, the Elves' secret reaches the Dwarves.
Now the finishing touches.
Who is it?
Well,
let's just call me a ghost.
I hope you have a good reason
for coming here uninvited.
I was hoping for a little game.
A game?
In which we bet information.
If I win, you share something, and vice versa.
You come here out of nowhere
and Nina Clive is supposed to take on the challenge?
Let me start with…
The Dwarves know about the existance of Aka Si Anse.
Sounds interesting?
As the lead researcher of Aka Si Anse theory
you should easily confirm the authenticity of this information.
Am I mistaken?
Alright.
Whoever you are, I can't ignore something like this.
Therefore, here is my wager.
The true lead researcher of Aka Si Anse–
Isn't you?
I already know about it.
And I know it's a lie.
And you have resorted to magic to make me believe it.
Now, what else do I have…
When the Dwarves learned about Áka Si Anse, they did not consider it a threat.
I bet the reason behind it.
They what?!
Far-fetched?
I possess details
about a weapon owned by the Dwarves,
which they believe to surpass the Áka Si Anse.
The E-bomb?
Yes.
A large-scale weapon that can wipe out an entire continent.
The most advanced technology in the history of the elves
and it was outperformed
by those moles burrowing in the earth?
Wait a moment.
A few times you played as if you were trying to lose.
Tell me one last thing.
Are you an enemy
or an ally?
I'm not your enemy,
nor your ally.
I just wish for none of you to die.
Very well Mr. Ghost.
You sure expect me to do something with all this information, don't you?
By the way,
Nina Clive is an alias.
You see, actually,
Think Nirvalen is my real name.
Unexpected, admit it!
Have you ever heard me call you Nina?
You had the audacity to treat me like your plaything
and I'll make you pay for it!
The rumor about elves being relentlessly vindictive
began with the Nirvalen family, you know.
Riku!
Riku, hurry! It's decontaminate.
Riku you lied! You said it'd be an hour.
Such a dose for two hours is insane!
I had no choice.
Without it, I would be detected in an instant.
Especially those with supreme intelligence,
wouldn't even consider such madness.
Riku!
It doesn't move anymore.
So, how much do you think I have left?
You won't die.
You have to stay alive until Schwi dies.
Ex-machina's lifespan… how long is it?
In solar cycles,
it's 892 years.
I really need to step it up then.
The first objective
removing the battle from human territory
complete.
First the Dwarfs, then the Elves.
Even the Werebeasts are leaving.
What in the world?
Lily, please stay on guard for me!
Huh? Wait a–
Couronne!
The ghosts' covert actions pressed on.
As expected, the Elves allied with the Fairies,
and to face the Dwarf fleet, they expanded contracts with the Dragonia.
Meanwhile, the Dwarves teamed up with the Giants
and turned many phantasmas to their side.
Manipulated by information,
each major pawn took precautions against the threat of another,
moving its forces to the continent of Ariena.
This place however, happens to be the base of the Flügel's sovereign,
the Old-deus,
Lord Artosh.
Umweg.
23 units ready.
9 remaining.
And thus, under the shadow of impending terror
the world began the countdown to the final battle.
Everything
as planned.
Hey Schwi,
is there like… a god of games?
If I said I'd seen him, would you believe me?
He always moved way beyond my predictions
and I always ended up losing.
And yet,
it was so much fun to play.
Next time…
Next time for sure I'll get him.
I always thought.
And now, I still need to settle things with him,
as that game from back then
isn't over yet.
You believe it,
then
I believe it too.
If you say he exists, then he does.
No doubt about it.
Damn it!
These words!
Why is there no one here to hear this?!
Riku!
Couron?
Just as you said
no one has died so far.
There are no sightings of other races either.
Thought so.
If you're the ones behind all of this,
I can’t express how incredible this is.
Still, Riku!
What in the world have you done to yourself?!
No big deal.
Like shit no big deal!
You're falling apart…
It's almost over.
Just let it go.
Almost over?
How long is that?
How much longer do I have to worry?
Hey, Couron
do you know what the gods are after in this war?
The title of the One.
Yeah, according to Schwi,
it's something called the Suniaster.
Many Old-deus emerged,
and in order for only one to rule, these wannabe gods established…
a conceptual device.
A conceptual device?
Where could something like that even be?
Suniaster's requirement:
It will manifest before the greatest power on the planet.
Thus, if there are ten gods with equal power,
I have to kill the other nine to become the One, right?
That's their way of thinking.
Wha— That's idiotic!
For such a dumb reason, we…
Couron, not even an idiot is that stupid.
After all,
you don't need any of this,
and Suniaster is still going to show up.
That's what we brought everyone together for.
Áka Si Anse,
Ether-bomb,
Heaven's Smite.
All these enormous powers, gathered for one purpose…
to break through
the planet.
The planet?!
All the Old Deus emerged from the planet.
Born from the Spirit Circuit.
Thus, the greatest power in the world is…
The Spirit Circuit.
We, the nobodies, are pulling the strings.
Using their own strength,
we'll turn the order of this world on its head.
Suniaster appears, and at this moment,
we become the One and fix the world.
To control the accumulated strikes,
we'll use power redirecting devices that Schwi has in her arsenal.
Umweg, 32 units,
precisely synchronized,
are capable of controlling the energy required to breaking the crust.
There are only nine left.
Once they're all set up…
checkmate.
They themselves will pierce through the planet,
and deliver Suniaster into our hands.
Without anyone dying.
I just can't wait to ask them.
Hey, hey, losers…
enjoying yourselves?
Riku?
Riku!
Did you tell anyone why you're leaving?
Not really.
They're probably all panicking by now.
They shouldn't be left alone for too long.
What now?!
You're the one who left them forever!
Forever…
Take care of Nonna and the others.
Riku, sleep.
I can't.
We need to hurry up and set up the rest.
Don't worry.
The battle won’t start anytime soon.
Your predictions covered everything.
But–
A little rest won’t hurt.
For you, we take a day off.
You're right.
Well, I'll focus on recovering today.
Yes.
Schwi,
sorry for being a burden.
Riku, you're lying down. It's not a burden.
Schwi,
I have a favor to ask.
When I'm sleeping…
will you hold my hand?
All the time,
don't be afraid, Riku.
Schwi, I’m so grateful that you came into my life.
I truly
love you.
I always will.
Riku,
forgive me.
I'll be back soon.
The Elves with their Áka Si Anse,
the Dwarfs with their Ether-bomb…
both wretched worms.
To stand against Lord Artosh,
you must be a total fool, nyan!
Ouch, nyan!
You're the fool, Azriel!
At this moment we can't afford any mistakes.
If Lord Artosh refrains from acting,
then we must wait as well.
Utterly boring, isn't it?
Idle mode.
I have to get this Suniaster, and Riku won't die.
Riku, hold on!
Oh my!
Are we having a solitary stroll today?
A faint spiritual reaction catches your eye, you come to take a look,
and what a wonderful bounty it turns out to be.
Pleasure to meet you, scrap.
Warning: Any hostile action will result in severe countermeasures.
From a single Prüfer, you say?
I've confirmed that there is no cluster activity within 100 km.
Then, it's truly a magnifique opportunité to pick up a premium head.
1: No one can be killed.
Luckily, Ex-Machinas don’t even possess the concept of death.
2: No one can be left to die.
Please, no futile–
I refuse!
Pardon?
This unit is disconnected,
it's worthless.
6: Breaking any of these rules results in a loss.
Therefore,
please, spare me.
No way, an Ex-machina that begs for its life?
M– m– moreover, a defect discarded by a cluster?!
I– It's the premium among the premiums!
Firepower comparison…
chances of survival:
none.
However,
they're never truly zero.
Laden: Code 1673B743E1F25 Script 3
Activate: Lösen.
Final warning.
All gear, armaments, maneuvers unrestricted.
Life preservation declared.
Oh dear… Ex-machinas are said to analyze and replicate
the techniques that were used against them.
Could it be that one of you died from laughter?
Over-boost!
Asyut-Armor!
Scattering dead spirits like that…
What an environmentally unfriendly machine.
Anyway,
that was supposed to stop me?
Never hoped for that.
Lösen: Enderpokryphen!
Einsweg.
Currently, her detection range matches my leap distance.
That means
Oh my!
Where are you off to?
Darn… I was aiming for the neck.
Could my hand have slipped?
No way a machine could have
anything like instinctive reflexes.
This is getting weird.
The head alone will be enough.
Let's make you a proper scrap
that silently rusts in the dirt.
Kein-Eintrag.
Riku...
I don't want to die.
I can't die!
They cannot fail
because of me!
The only thing left for me…
All I can do for Riku now…
Identification number:
Übercluster 207 Prüfer 4F57T9.
To Eins: requesting reconnection.
Heart analysis completed.
Initiate synchronization!
Due to prolonged disconnection, your data is presumed
to contain numerous critical errors.
Request rejected.
Response rejected!
Forward this to Einzig.
Your unit has no permissions to reject any reports!
Urgent reapplication!
Synchronize!
Eins...
no, correction...
you dense asshole!
I meant to never share this with anyone!
I love Riku, I don’t want to part with him.
It's embarrassing…
All these contradictions I got from him…
All… all of this is mine alone!
I'm telling you to take it!
Get the meaning of it, idiot!
Stop giving me shit,
and carry it on!
The unit is clearly defective.
I know.
Ambiguous, incoherent, yet still functional.
Abnormal.
I know that too!
Impossible to occur.
It's the truth…
The heart that Riku gives me is the proof!
Your unit
contains valuable data.
Synchronization initiated.
Completion in 251 seconds.
During this time, destruction is prohibited.
Alles-Lösen.
Forme – unpredictable threat protocol:
initiate.
That urge, the heart…
Born as a tool, I found meaning.
And all of that
in these 251 seconds
will emerge!
Are those giagantic wings
suppose to be a jab?
For a mere puppet, quite impressive.
Schwi.
Pardon?
I didn’t mention my name,
so here it is.
A gift from Riku,
my precious self.
I see. My name is Jibril.
Pleased to meet you.
And now
I bid you farewell.
Stay off their stage,
never give up the initiative.
Make them reckless,
let them dismiss you as a threat.
Fill them with doubt,
let them think they can't make a mistake.
If you lose now… prepare for the next!
I can't die!
Not yet!
I can't die yet!
Umweg!
Finally a proper mistake.
You really gave me a hassle.
Mistake?
What are you talking about…
Very well then.
Sorry for calling you scrap.
I take that back.
You lady, are a threat that must be eliminated at once.
An enemy worthy of the full extent of my power.
Synchronization complete.
In this game,
victory goes to me.
Lösen: Kein-Eintrag.
Riku…
Hey, Riku…
Schwi
has understood at last.
is really blissful to have met you.
In the next one
we'll never be apart.
Know that
I trully love you.
I didn't get the head… everything is shattered.…
and that energy outburst turned me into a brat.
All of that
ended up being utterly pointless!
I really thought…
we could win this…
having Schwi… and the others.
I don't know what god out there created us, but…
hey… I'm begging you…
just one time…
Can’t I win even one damn time?
If… that’s so…
what did you give me that heart for!
Schwi…
why?
You have to stay alive until Schwi dies.
Ah, right…
If Schwi is dead, it's fine.
Now I can just…
Spieler Riku.
Who are you…
I have no name,
but they call me with Einzig.
Player Schwi entrusted me with her will, which I've come to fulfill.
Schwi…
Rule 2: bla bla bla bla
The rule set by Riku.
The loss of a tool
doesn't qualify as a losing condition.
The loss of Schwi doesn't qualify.
Check, Riku.
Take care of the rest.
Providing additional information:
1: Currently, Umweg installation points have drawn the attention of several races,
and any activity will lead to Cluster exposure,
resulting in combat with probability of 98%.
Consequently, only the already deployed Umwegs are available for use,
with the amount of 24 being insufficient to redirect the energy down into the planet.
However, it's possible to direct it southwest.
2: We Ex-Machina, are able to process received damage
and deploy a weapon to replicate it.
Its wielder, Spieler Riku, shall pierce the planet,
thereby manifesting the Suniaster in his hands.
We are Ex-machina, machines bereft of heart…
mere tools.
Created solely to be used at another's discretion.
And so, Spieler Riku,
refine the strategy.
Your orders.
Schwi…
The rules… don't include
the loss…
of a tool.
Schwi...
If that is what you wish…
then so do I.
So cute, nyaa!
That restoration procedure is such a pain!
It's been so long since I was able to see my Jibi like this!
But that scrap… what was it up to, nyaa?
Multiple heat sources detected at the rear!
It's—
Wーwha— what the nyaa?!
Who fired the Heaven's Smite, nyaa!
Preemptive strike detected from Avant Heim.
Arm the Ether-bombs!
Áka Si Anse, initiate guidance phase!
Starboard, Artosh. Port, the Dwarf fleet.
Preemptive strike from Avantheim?
No… this is…
You dare to mess with us nyaa… scrap heaps!
Artosh-sama?
I've awaited you, my destined enemy.
Indeed, it's but natural for the strongest to be opposed by the weakest.
Right, monkey?
An attack from behind Avant Heim was launched without killing anyone,
and with it…
Cluster 11 relocating: set point.
…the final clash of powers will begin at any moment.
All units, form up.
We face the Old-deus.
The petty plan of mere humans will be
a breeze for him to see through.
And yet, he'll bring all his power to wipe us out.
That's the custom of the mighty.
That's how the mighty think.
You should know your place, you insolent specks of filth.
Flounder, writhe,
and find out at last that no amount of crawling worms shall ever match the heavens.
Áka Si Anse, full salvo launch!
Ether-bomb, full-force strike!
God's Smite.
Áka Si Anse, even with the power of the Ether-Bomb,
was but a shadow before the Godly Smite of Artosh.
All that energy collided… merged…
becoming the light heralding the demise of this world.
Then…
It's moving away?
that energy…
We are the machines, tools bereft of heart.
Having lived without life,
we die having one.
Aus.
Jawohl!
Cluster 11 – contribution from 4807 units.
Copying, layout reproduction completed,
synchronizing.
Lösen:
Origin 0000:
The Reaper of Planets – Stalemartyr,
it's yours.
Alright,
that makes it a draw…
a stalemate.
Pardon me, oh mighty gods.
Suniaster…
How many had to die for this moment?
Schwi's comrades…
each a living being…
How many
have I sent to their deaths?!
I lied to my own damn self!
Took Schwi's wish as an excuse!
How—
dare you call this a draw!
Schwi!
Forgive me, Schwi…
I lost again.
Oh, Schwi…
if you and I
could only be together
to win in the next one, Schwi…
In the game where no one has to die.
If a wish were to bring forth a god…
God of Games!
Even if my life means nothing,
I offer all of it in prayer for the first time!
I beg you!
If you deem
a wretched loser taking the Grail an abomination!
If you deem these hands too stained in blood!
Please!
Tell me at least
that what we've done meant something!
I don’t care who!
Anyone who can end this cursed war!
Take that Suniaster!
Anyone!
Knew it… you were really there.
Hey, let's have one more game.
In this one we’ll show you we can win.
Together with Schwi,
it's certain.
When I was a child,
I thought the world was much simpler.
That no battle is unwinnable,
every effort is rewarded,
and everything is possible.
I looked through eyes untried by reality.
And well…
Checkmate,
right, Riku?
In case… everything works out,
can you move the white rook to E6 for me?
Couronne Dola,
I mean—
Sister,
the rest… I leave in your hands.
Thanks for everything up until now.
Hey Riku, Schwi,
you two really did something incredible.
You put an end to the eternal war.
And still—
it's weird.
Why for your sister…
Why does this feel so unbearable?!
The game isn’t over yet.
It’s not checkmate. It's check.
But this…
puts us in a perpetual check.
It’s the first time you’ve drawn with me!
Created by no one.
Wished for by no one.
Prayed for by no one.
Purely of your own will,
you went from beasts to walking on two legs.
Attaining knowledge and becoming
what you are today. A nameless race.
But I, the one true god, shall give you a name.
Immanity.
And so.
To all exceed, the self appointed sentient races.
First, there was ascheito, to honor the fallen.
Then aschento, for unification within the races,
but now in abidance with the ten pledges,
you will now say aschente.
As of this day, the world will be forever changed!
Now lets keep this game going!
So about that story,
how much of it was true and how much was a lie?
Oh Izuna, if I told the whole truth, it wouldn't
be an unspoken myth now anymore, would it?
You can be a real jerk, you know that?
But you are good at petting, so I'll forgive you.
Izuna!
Sora, Shiro, Steph.
Oh jeez, where the heck did you go?
You really gotta look out, there's a
bunch of creeps out there you know.
Someone like Sora, or someone like Shiro?
He ran off while still in the lead—
They're absolutely right Izuna, there are
more creeps like those two in this world. Ah...
Oh my god, what are you doing?!
What is that writing?
Jibril.
Hi. Hello hello!
Can you read this?
Oh it's an ancient language from way
back before Immanity became united.
Come to think of it, all my current
problems are this idiot's fault.
It says, Couronne Dola, Riku Dola and Schwi Dola.
Couronne Dola?
Yes, she was the Queen of Elkia
that established the country.
She was smart and full of joy,
and a bright soul that was never seen crying.
She was the pride of the Dola family.
And who are the other two?
I have no idea.
Schwi—
That machine was not an Immanity though.
I feel like I've heard that name before..
At least, I think so.
As it turns out, the world
really isn't all that complicated.
It's pretty simple actually.
It's all just a game. A very simple game.
Of course, some will try to make it difficult.
But you can handle them. I know it.
I know you can!
Now—
Let's get this game started!